chessmaniac.com 2013-03-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**The ChessManiac.com Privacy Policy**

ChessManiac.com is committed to preserving your privacy online. When you visit our site, we collect two types of information from you: 1) specific information you voluntarily submit and 2) general information our site gathers automatically. Specific Information You Submit If your email ChessManiac.com for any reason, the information in your email will only be used by us to contact you directly. We will keep your information on file only for the purpose of providing service. We may also share some of your information with third parties that are directly involved with support issues, such as product technical support. We will never willfully disclose any individually identifiable information to any other third parties without a user's specific permission to do so. We do not sell users' names or email addresses to other companies. We will only provide individually identifiable information to third parties only where it is required by law. 3) We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml>   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here < [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org%3E/)>   
To opt-out of receiving Cookies from third party advertising networks click [ here.](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)   
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org%3E/)  
We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit    
4) Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Email move notification**

If you opt in to our email move notification you will receive an email with the chess move that has been made by your opponent.

**How to opt out of the email notification system**

If you wish to no longer get messages from our system you will need to log in to your account and navigate to your setting page. The url of the settings page is http://www.chessmaniac.com/webchess/configure.php From this page you can opt out of the email move notification system by selecting the correct option. 

**General Information We Gather**

As you browse our Web site, we collect standard tracking data, which we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns. Furthermore, cookies and/or web beacons collect data in the ad serving process. This information is aggregated with tracking data from all site visitors. We use such aggregated information to help us evaluate our site and to improve our services to clients. 

**Third Party Links**

This site contains external links to other web sites, such as (but not limited to) other chess related resources. ChessManiac.com has no control over the content of third party sites and is not responsible for any information or content contained on these sites, nor is ChessManiac.com responsible for the privacy policies of those sites and the information they may gather expressly or automatically 

If you have any problems please [Contact Us](http://www.chessmaniac.com/mailform.php "Privacy Policy")
